♪Destiny is so mysterious♪
♪Hazards appear in piles♪
♪Reflected in the mirror of mortal♪
♪Reincarnation repeats itself♪
♪I'm so forlorn and no one responds♪
♪Twilight falls on the deserted path♪
♪Beautiful old memories♪
♪Echo under the eaves♪
♪I don't want my soul to perish♪
♪Or disappear♪
♪Always live the life, happy or sad♪
♪Get rid of the glory♪
♪Reveal the destiny♪
♪Absorb the luck of heaven and earth♪
♪And prosper perfectly♪
♪When young dream chasers♪
♪Travel together♪
♪And shine brightly♪
♪I keep them company for mankind♪
♪Waiting to emerge♪
♪However the world changes♪
♪I've never been afraid♪
♪Even if everything collapses in the end♪
♪I will hold you in my arms♪
♪Brambles pierce through me♪
♪Tears roll down your cheeks♪
=The Last Immortal=
=Episode 33=
♪Witness several rounds of
bright moon rolls♪
♪Never touched
by the worldly wind and snow♪
♪Endless yearning♪
♪Is hidden in the day and night♪
♪Time passes by in an instant♪
♪Let the longing be as high as the sky♪
Why are you drinking alone without me?
I'm fine.
I'm just thinking about something.
It's about Hong Yi, isn't it?
I know you've been with him
for a thousand years in this cottage.
You're more than friends.
But the pear blossoms only remind him of you,
not me.
I'm sorry.
I'm only getting married to him
to find the devil cultivator.
And once we find him,
my marriage to him will...
I know.
But he's so happy even if your marriage
is fake.
Yan Shuang, you know
Hong Yi has always been a friend to me.
And I think his feelings for you are...
Don't be so tense, dummy.
It's not your fault.
It's just wishful thinking for him
and me alike.
It's not up to us
whom we like or not.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm ready to let him go.
If you've really let go,
why are you drinking here?
It's kind of a farewell ceremony.
You know I used to be playful.
I couldn't let go of Hong Yi,
or perform my duty.
The Eagle Clan is declining
and the devils are on the move.
I must go back and perform my duty.
I'm ready to return and take over
the throne of the Eagle Clan.
As for all the petty love affairs,
it's no longer worth the Queen's while
to think about it.
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
You are now the Phoenix Queen.
Hong Yi has also become the Demon King.
We all do our jobs,
taking up the slack in the clan.
How can I still be as unmotivated
as I was before?
Don't worry, after I become
the Eagle Queen,
I'm gonna be good and do great things.
Drink with me.
Your Majesty is going to marry
the Phoenix Queen?
It's a ploy to find out the devil spy.
It's confidential. I'd like to ask you
to personally make the arrangements.
Don't let anyone know.
You've been with Yin
for a thousand years.
Though the original purpose
is to find out the devil spy,
you've gotten what you wanted.
You don't look as happy
as I thought you were.
You won't believe what I'm about to say.
All I could think about before
was to catch the culprit at the wedding
while the god light shines
and avenge my aunt and Yin.
I never thought about getting
what I wanted.
Yin and Feng Yin are different to me
after all.
Yin is cute and passionate.
Feng Yin is rational and calm.
She's too sensible to even get close to.
She has become Feng Yin,
the Queen of the Phoenix Clan,
admired by many.
You're not used to it, right?
I was surely happy that she returned
and became the Phoenix Queen.
It's just because I've wronged Yin.
I've always kept her in my heart.
Now I see she's doing well.
I don't think there's anything
to worry about.
Of course.
It's nice to see Yuan Qi sulking.
I'll help you prepare for the wedding.
Shu,
what brings you back to Bainiao Island
all of a sudden?
Father, do you know that Feng Ming was
killed by a devil cultivator last night?
What? Who is the murderer?
I wanted to ask you this yesterday
in the hall.
When Lan Feng was killed,
there was a black shadow behind him.
Do you know who that was?
How could I know?
You don't suspect me, do you?
A devil cultivator who also has access
to both the Heavenly Palace and Prison.
I have to rule out every suspect.
I can't believe you doubted
your own father.
I just want to know the truth.
Alright.
I'll show you the truth.
(Open to Good Advice)
See for yourself.
Lan Feng.
Lan Feng shows signs of life.
Do the devils really have a way
to bring Lan Feng back to life?
Definitely.
Shu,
Lan Feng is my son-in-law.
For the sake of your happiness,
how could I harm him?
I've been saving him
for a thousand years.
If I were the murderer, how would I
want him to come back to life?
I practiced devil magic to save
myself and others.
What's wrong with that?
Father, I'm just afraid that
you're involved in this.
I'm sorry, Father.
Never mind.
Now, amid internal and external threats,
you and I must work together
to get through this.
I've been thinking. Feng Yin wasn't there
when it all happened a thousand years ago.
Why would she help Qing Yi and Yin
from Daze Mountain?
I guess she's using them against me.
But if other immortals were involved
in Lan Feng's death,
I want to get them too.
Since Yuan Qi wants to find out
what happened back then, I'll help him.
I had some trouble with him
the other day.
I can get closer to
and reconcile with him
in this investigation.
By the way, I can find out
what else Feng Yin is up to.
Your Godship,
I found this from the sealed files
of the Heavenly Palace.
You may find the investigation file useful.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
If you need anything, please let me know.
I'll do my best to help.
You're just in time. I do have
something to ask you.
When Emperor Lan Feng died,
many fairy maids of the Heavenly Palace
were relegated for their mistakes,
especially the ones on duty
at Lingyu Hall.
But whatever they did wrong
isn't recorded,
not even their whereabouts. Why?
The Wind Lord helped to investigate.
There was indeed a lot of chaos in
the Immortal Realm in those days.
They made frequent mistakes due to this.
Including your maid Hongque?
She was guarding Emperor Lan Feng's
ice coffin.
But the coffin was damaged
due to her negligence.
My father found it in time. Otherwise,
Lan Feng's remains would be...
She deserved to be punished by being
removed of her immortal bones
and sent down to the Mortal Realm
forever.
Your Godship.
Your Godship,
a message has come from the Phoenix Clan.
It says
the Phoenix Queen and the Demon King
are getting married.
Getting married?
Feng Yin and Hong Yi are to be married
in seven days.
The Three Lower Realms
have been notified.
This is the invitation they gave you.
(The Phoenix Queen
and the Demon King's Wedding)
A thousand years ago, on the day
Feng Yin was born,
Fox Queen Hong Ruo brought Hong Yi
to Wutong Island to propose marriage.
And Feng Yin became close to Hong Yi
soon after her return.
If you think about it,
this marriage isn't so surprising.
A Demon King and a Phoenix Queen
are a perfect match.
(Invitation)
Your Godship, are you all right?
Your Godship.
(Wedding Plan
Wedding at the Heavenly Square)
All right, that's it.
Inform the Three Realms of my betrothal
to the Demon King.
- Yes.
- Feng Yin.
Your Godship.
Why would you marry Hong Yi?
Since you're here,
let's talk about some business.
What business?
That's what I came to ask.
Answer me.
I don't need to discuss whom I marry
with you, do I?
But you and Jiu are just friends, aren't you?
We are.
But we've got time to develop love.
Yin.
Don't marry someone else.
I'm not Yin.
- Let go.
- No.
I've waited so long for your return.
I don't want to let go.
I'm afraid you've forgotten
what you said.
You said a Water Divine Beast's life
is only a brief moment in yours.
Though Yin and I are fellow disciples
in the same sect,
she's just a passerby in my life.
All the things about Jin are just a flash
in the pan with no memory left.
Now I am Feng Yin,
a demigod.
Is that why you come back to me?
It's not like that.
I said those words because...
Because what?
Anyway, it was my fault.
Whether it was or not,
it's not important.
(Celebrate the peace of the immortals
and the demons)
Why are you worried, Father?
When Feng Yin marries Hong Yi,
she and Yuan Qi will be impossible.
Isn't this a good thing for us?
It's not that simple.
The Phoenix Queen is getting married soon
after she proposed to reopen the case.
The wedding must have something
to do with the case.
Shu, I'm afraid this will not only
affect your bid for Heavenly Empress,
but also delay Lan Feng's resurrection.
No,
there must be no mistake
about the two plans.
We must find out what they're up to.
(I don't believe there's no inside story
to this marriage.)
(I'm going to find out what's going on
with these two.)
His Lordship Lin Mo says Your Majesty
need to choose the robe for the wedding.
Please select the gifts for the wedding.
During the wedding, you and
the Phoenix Queen need to exchange gifts.
Your Majesty will decide it to show
your sincerity.
Did you see Yan Shuang?
Why didn't she come?
Your Majesty.
Her Highness said
she was busy and couldn't come.
Didn't you tell her it was urgent?
I need her help
with the wedding arrangement.
I did.
I stood her up once,
and she's done with me.
You may go.
Your Majesty.
His Lordship said
you should make early decisions
before late.
Alright, got it.
Yes.
Your Highness, the Demon King
is waiting outside.
Tell him I'm busy.
Yes.
Are you done?
So are you free?
I told you to...
I'm willing to wait.
I kept you waiting last time.
So I made it up to you three times over.
Can we have peace?
Look how the flowers have wilted
while I waited for you.
Have something to eat.
You're too devoted
to the official business.
Are you here to eat with me?
Come on.
You don't know how tiresome it is
to arrange a wedding.
They ask me every day,
"Will this work? Is that alright?"
It's giving me a headache.
So help me out here. Help me choose.
Do it on your own.
I've come to beg for your help.
Are you still my friend?
It depends on you.
I'm still busy. Goodbye.
Yan Shuang, I'll be mad at you.
There's a lot of talk in the Three Realms
about Feng Yin's marriage.
Looks like she's serious
about marrying Hong Yi.
Hong Yi. You two seem close, huh?
Can't you tell whose side you're on?
Jiu used to be good to Martial Aunt Yin.
To find her for the past thousand years,
he also planted a pear tree for her
in the Mortal Realm.
Is she really touched by his affection?
Found it.
Are you listening to us or not,
Martial Uncle?
They're getting married for the god
light.
- God light?
When immortal and demon demigods
get married, there will be god light.
They're trying to find the devil.
I knew Feng Yin wouldn't
marry Hong Yi for love.
Look at this.
Though we know the truth, there's nothing
we can do to stop the wedding.
Yes, Martial Aunt Yin is quite different now.
No one can stop her from doing
what she wants to do.
The gown is ready, Your Majesty.
All right.
You may go.
Yes.
(Fengyi Palace)
Feng Yin.
What's on your mind?
Why did you come to Wutong Island again?
I know why you want to get married.
The fake marriage
is to draw god light, right?
You've got a lot of nerve.
The Ancestral God is looking forward
to it.
But all you want is the god light.
You'll be punished.
Don't bother to worry about me.
If only I can find the person,
I will take any punishment.
Then why don't you choose me?
Marrying me can also get you
the god light, can't it?
(Fengyi Palace)
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm perfectly serious.
I'm the son of True Gods.
It'll be easier for me to survive
the punishment.
It'd give you the idea that all the women
in the world want to marry you.
I've made up my mind.
Say no more.
Feng Yin.
Yuan Qi.
Don't be a philanderer on Wutong Island.
Untie me.
I simply don't want to.
I didn't mean to harass you.
But it turns out to be a good idea.
You seem to have forgotten that
the Fire Phoenix is meant to be the
divine beast of the True God of Chaos.
You should follow my orders.
Now I order you to come back
to Qingchi Palace with me.
What are you doing?
Hey!
Yuan Qi.
Your Godship.
What's wrong with Her Majesty?
Feng Yin has offended me.
I'm taking her back to Qingchi Palace
to punish her.
- Punish?
- Put me down.
- Your Godship, don't.
- Yuan Qi.
Look how jealous he is.
Your Majesty, how can you smile?
Lady Feng Yin is being carried away.
He is the True God.
What can I do about it?
Let's stay out of the young people's
business.
Let me down!
Yuan Qi.
What are you trying to do?
This is a piece of Feng Ming's
immortal spirit. It stores
(Lustrous Moon)
his last memory before he died.
Just give me a few days
to complete the formation.
Then we'll get a clue to the murderer.
You wouldn't have to marry Hong Yi,
would you?
You have your way. I have my plans.
You don't really believe that
I'm marrying Hong Yi
just to find the devil cultivator,
do you?
Do you have other plans?
It's not something you should worry about.
- Then I...
- Stop it.
Yuan Qi? What are you doing here?
You're marrying Feng Yin tomorrow.
Why don't you have a drink with me?
Do we know each other well?
You're drunk on love.
Do you think it's a good idea to come
to me, the groom?
Hong Yi,
we've been through thick and thin
together, haven't we?
Feng Yin has chosen you.
I've decided to give up.
But the good thing is
I'm sure you'll be good to her.
Absolutely.
But if you dare to
put her through any harm,
I'm definitely coming for you.
You're such a nosy True God.
Don't worry.
I won't give you this chance.
Great.
Drink.
Hong Yi.
How long has it been
since we've had a drink together?
It's so melodramatic.
I insisted on performing the Heavenly
Thunder punishment on you back then.
It almost killed you.
I regret it.
I've been trying to find a chance to
come here and apologize to you.
But so much has happened since then.
I haven't been able
to apologize to you in person.
So you've come to apologize to me?
Sort of.
At least the apology is genuine.
That's true.
I can tell if you're sincere or not.
My good friend.
Yuan Qi,
you don't have to apologize to me.
Instead, I'm the one who should
apologize.
There are many excuses.
But no matter what,
I'm responsible for the massacre
of Daze Mountain.
I'm in debt to the whole sect,
especially Xian Shan and Xian Zhu.
Why are you getting soberer?
It's getting late.
I should go back.
Hope everything goes well
at your wedding tomorrow.
Have you known everything?
You don't have to hide it from me.
Feng Yin told me the plan.
It's easy to get the god light.
But I'm not sure if the other plan can
come to fruition.
Don't worry.
Parasol is originally from
the God Realm.
Fuchen can grow into a parasol tree.
When the tree absorbs the god light,
it can use the God Realm's tracking
technique to find Purple Moon.
You don't have to worry about it.
Sleep well.
You also came.
It's been a long time.
Yeah.
Elder Mu Ling.
He has been missing for days.
Why is he here all of a sudden?
There's devil energy left in him.
Something's wrong here.
Elder Bei Cang?
We're in a spell formation.
The spiritual power is useless here.
Get out of here!
Your Highness!
Father.
The wedding is about to begin.
Do you know what they're planning?
The guards in ambush near Eagle Island
have just sent back news.
Yan Shuang has fallen into the trap.
We're one step away.
But the other sects have already left.
If we're late for too long,
the Peacock Clan will be criticized.
Why don't I go ahead
and give you some cover?
Let me know when you've found out
their intentions.
I'll improvise.
That's the only way now.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Don't be over-courteous.
It's a happy day for Wutong Island,
so make yourselves at home.
- Greetings, Your Majesty!
The time has come to welcome
the Phoenix Queen.
Greetings, Phoenix Queen.
Rise.
(Where's Hong Yi?)
Your Majesty.
Wake up, Your Majesty.
It's going to be late
for the auspicious time.
Why are you all here?
Your Majesty, you've finally woken up.
It's 9:45 and we're going to be late
for the wedding ceremony.
9:45?
Why didn't you wake me up earlier?
Why hasn't the Demon King
arrived yet?
Where's the groom at this hour?
What kind of man would be late
for his wedding?
This Demon King is so cocky.
I've heard that this marriage
is an exchange of favors.
Judging from the Demon King's attitude,
it's true he doesn't want to marry her.
Che, don't talk nonsense.
This is nonsense!
The Demon King is too disrespectful.
Right.
It's not polite.
We've waited for so long.
Yuan Qi, you gave me the strongest wine.
You'll be dead by the time
the wedding is over.
Devil?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please save
Princess Yan Shuang.
What's happened to her?
We were drawn to a trap by the devil
on our way to your wedding
with the Phoenix Queen.
The casualties are heavy.
Her Highness...
Where is she?
Right over there.
Your Majesty.
His Majesty must have been drunk
and missed the auspicious time.
I don't know where he's been
since he sobered up.
(Yan Shuang is also absent.)
(What happened?)
Is the Demon King trying to
break up the wedding?
I can't believe the Phoenix Queen is
abandoned by her groom on her wedding day.
It's a disgrace.
If the Demon King doesn't want
to marry her,
why did he agree to this marriage
in the first place?
Because I'm the one who didn't want
him to come.
Greetings, Your Godship.
All rise.
I made the Demon King drunk.
I'm afraid he won't be able to make it
to the wedding.
We were wrong about him.
Hong Yi told me about your second plan
when he was drunk.
You want to use the parasol tree to absorb
god light to find Purple Moon.
I can help you, too.
We've had at least one experience
with marriage.
It's a fake wedding anyway.
Am I not better than Hong Yi?
You're better than anyone
at being a scoundrel.
Your Godship, the Demon King is drunk
and late for the wedding.
He has no regard for the Immortal Realm.
We can't let the Phoenix Queen
suffer this insult.
I think we should call it quits.
You don't have to excuse
the Demon King anymore.
The engagement is naturally off the table.
Otherwise, I'll have robbed the bride
today for nothing.
Rob the bride?
Rob?
Rob? That's something.
He wants to rob the bride.
What's going on?
Since you're all here,
listen up, it's not that the Demon King
doesn't want to come.
I went to great lengths to get him drunk.
He can't come.
I've been in love with the Phoenix Queen
for a long time.
I didn't expect the Demon King
to get the upper hand.
So I had to do this.
♪Witness several rounds of
bright moon rolls♪
♪Never touched
by the worldly wind and snow♪
♪Endless yearning♪
♪Is hidden in the day and night♪
♪Time passes by in an instant♪
♪Let the longing be as high as the sky♪
♪May I become a wisp of smoke,
lingering around your lips♪
Are you alright?
♪Carries many karmic cycles♪
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
You're a real pain.
I was late for my wedding to save you.
You have to remember the favor I did you.
♪Outlining your silhouette in memories♪
Whatever, let's get you home.
No, thanks.
I'm afraid it's too much of a favor
for me to repay.
Besides, it's your wedding day.
The devils are trying to stop
your wedding.
Aren't you in a hurry to get married?
What are you doing here?
♪Across rivers and mountains♪
Alright, I should go.
♪Far from the light♪
♪I look back
and find your familiar smile♪
♪Between Heaven and Earth♪
♪Only the moon and the mountains
connect you and me♪
Today you're all here.
I'd like to ask you all to be
my witnesses.
(Qingchi Palace)
I'd like to offer the entire Qingchi Palace
to marry into Wutong Island.
Marry into Wutong Island?
How can he do this?
He can't do this!
Will Your Majesty
take me as your husband?
Everyone is watching.
Don't make me look bad.
First things first. Let's get married.
We need god light to find
the Purple Moon.
That's important.
♪The night breeze blows♪
♪Look at the moon in my dream♪
God Yuan Qi
♪With your eyes in my heart♪
is deeply in love with me.
You're all here today to witness it.
Yuan Qi will now be my husband
and live on Wutong Island.
That's great.
♪We continue to enjoy an ordinary life♪
Martial Aunt is majestic.
(Qingchi Palace)
♪All I want is to walk around with you♪
We've been given
such a great honor today.
♪Don't let the story wait for no reason♪
Let's finish the ceremony.
♪Finally I see the moonlight♪
♪The night breeze blows♪
♪Look at the moon in my dream♪
♪With your eyes in my heart♪
♪How can I not think of you?♪
♪Luckily in the world♪
♪You and I witness how time goes by♪
♪We continue to enjoy an ordinary life♪
♪All I want is to visit you often♪
♪And see the world with you♪
♪All I want is to walk around with you♪
Let Heaven and Earth bear witness today.
I, Yuan Qi, and Feng Yin are married.
I will protect Feng Yin
for the rest of my life
until the day I die.
♪Flowers bloom, hands hold♪
♪I look into your eyes♪
♪Life after life, I search♪
♪Reminiscence and nostalgia♪
♪Your smile is my sweetest dream♪
♪On a chilly night, leaves gyrate♪
♪Your face emerges♪
♪Life after life, I get disappointed♪
♪Old dreams come back to me♪
♪Your heart is where I stay alone♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I water the withered with the ocean♪
♪Make vibrant changes♪
♪And rebuild love♪
♪Who said♪
♪Flowers and leaves never meet♪
♪Life and death never interfere♪
♪I bid farewell with blood and tears♪
♪Unshackle the regret♪
♪And rush to you forever♪
♪Forever♪